let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which artist released the album Lover ?",
    answer: "Taylor Swift",
    options: [
        "Taylor Swift",
        "Beyoncé",
        "Ed Sheeran",
        "Ariana Grande"
    ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which album won the Grammy Award for Album of the Year in 2020?",
        answer: "When We All Fall Asleep, Where Do We Go?  by Billie Eilish",
        options: [
            "Golden Hour by Kacey Musgraves",
            "When We All Fall Asleep, Where Do We Go?  by Billie Eilish",
            "thank u, next by Ariana Grande",
            "Cuz I Love You by Lizzo"
        ]
      },
        {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Who released the album folklore in 2020?",
        answer: "Taylor Swift",
        options: [
            "Harry Styles",
            "Lady Gaga",
            "Lana Del Rey",
            "Taylor Swift"
        ]
      },
        {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which artist recently announced a world tour for 2023?",
        answer: "Adele",
        options: [
            "Bruno Mars",
            "Adele",
            "Justin Bieber",
            "Drake"
            ]
      },
        {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which album featured the hit song Drivers License",
        answer: "SOUR by Olivia Rodrigo",
        options: [
            "SOUR by Olivia Rodrigo",
            "EVERMORE by Taylor Swift", 
            "FUTURE NOSTALGIA by Dua Lipa",
            "POSITIONS by Ariana Grande"
            ]
      },
      {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Who won the Best New Artist award at the 2021 Grammy Awards?",
        answer: "Megan Thee Stallion",
        options: [
            "Megan Thee Stallion",
            "Doja Cat",
            "Phoebe Bridgers",
            "Roddy Ricch"
            ]
      },
      {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which artist released the album Happier Than Ever in 2021?",
        answer: "Billie Eilish",
        options: [
            "Billie Eilish",
            "Halsey",
            "Selena Gomez",
            "Shawn Mendes"
            ]
      },
      {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Who recently broke the record for the most-streamed album by a female artist in its first week?",
        answer: "Taylor Swift",
        options: [
            "Cardi B",
            "Adele",
            "Taylor Swift",
            "Beyoncé"
            ]
      },
      {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which album featured the song Blinding Lights ?",
        answer: "AFTER HOURS by The Weeknd",
        options: [
            "AFTER HOURS by The Weeknd",
            "FINE LINE by Harry Styles",
            "FOLKLORE by Taylor Swift",
            "CHROMATICA by Lady Gaga"
            ]
      },
      {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Who became the youngest artist to win the Grammy Award for <b> Album of the Year?",
        answer: "Billie Eilish",
        options: [
            "Billie Eilish",
            "Taylor Swift",
            "Lorde",
            "Adele"
            ]
      },
]